You@Come on
You@Hurry up
You@Take it deeper
You@Yes
You@That's it
You@Move faster
You@Take it all the way
You@Hurry up, you little slut
You@Look at me
You@Don't stop your mouth
You@Take it all in
You@Very good
You@That's it
You@I love seeing your expression when you're stuffed full
You@You need to go faster
You@Look at me, yes
You@That's it
You@Excellent
You@Take it deeper
You@Swallow it all
You@Faster
You@I can't take it anymore
You@Yes, just like that
You@You're doing great
You@You're performing very well
Samantha@You suddenly changed into a different person
Samantha@And you've become too aggressive all of a sudden
You@Not at all, you look so beautiful like this
You@Hurry up
You@I want more
You@Again